I see the warning on the console screen
You're pulling harder than I've ever seen
I'm caught inside the gravity well A one-way
ticket on a carousel The navigation is totally
blind I'm leaving all the safety behind
Structural integrity is starting to bend I'm
accelerating faster to the bitter end You're a
massive body, I'm a satellite I'm breaking into
pieces in the dead of night We crossed the road's
limit Tearing me apart Tearing me apart
We crossed the roach limit A fatal attraction, a
heavy heart There's no surviving when you get
this close A total system failure, a lethal dose
Yeah, we crossed the roach limit
The telemetry spinning into the red
I should've listened to the things they said But
the magnetic field is pulling me in I feel the
friction underneath my skin I'm caught in the
orbit of a dangerous star Structural integrity
is starting to bend I'm accelerating faster to
the bitter end You're a massive body, I'm a
satellite I'm breaking into pieces in the dead
of night We crossed the roach limit Tearing me
apart Tearing me apart
We cross the roach limit A fatal attraction, a
heavy heart There's no surviving when you get
this close A total system failure, a lethal dose
Yeah, we cross the roach limit
We crossed the roach limit Tearing me apart,
tearing me apart
We crossed the roach limit A fatal attraction, a
heavy heart There's no surviving when you get
this close A total system failure, a lethal dose
Yeah, we cross the road's limit Tearing me apart
System failure